my-tools-app.com 2012-01-30

# My Tools

## My-tools-app Privacy Statement

My-tools-app (“Licensor”, “We” or “Us”) is the licensor of this plugin (the “Plugin”). This Privacy Policy is a binding part of Licensor’s License and Terms of Use, and explains the type of information We collects through its website and browser companion software (“Plugin Service”) and what We do with it. If you download and use our Plugin Service software or use our website (the “Site”), you will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may collect certain information about your web usage and sites you have visited, which may be shared with third parties and used for advertising. NOTE: THE PLUGIN COLLECTS AND STORES INFORMATION CONCERNING THE WEB PAGES YOU VISIT AND YOUR ACTIVITY ON THOSE PAGES, SUCH AS IMPRESSIONS, CLICKS AND SEARCH TERMS. IN SOME CASES, INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE PLUGIN SERVICE MAY BE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AND IN SOME CASES INFORMATION (INCLUDING INFORMATION FROM OR ABOUT PAGES OF SOCIAL MEDIA WEBSITES YOU VISIT) MAY BE USED OR SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR PURPOSES OF DISPLAYING TARGETED ADVERTISEMENTS PROMOTIONAL AND MARKETING MATERIAL TO YOU. HOWEVER, YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US, AND WE DO NOT ATTEMPT TO ANALYZE WEB USAGE DATA TO DETERMINE THE INDIVIDUAL IDENTITY OF ANY PLUGIN. What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our application (we continually strive to improve our application offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

**To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

**To send periodic emails**   
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

### Do we use cookies?

We do use cookies.

### Third Party Collection

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential (“Third Parties”). These Third Parties may send (or “serve”) advertisements directly to your browser, from our Site, our Plugin Service, and from other websites and automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Information concerning these Third Parties practices is not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. We may also release your information when we believe that such release is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements)(ii) protect the safety and security of users of the our services or members of the public(iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposesor (iv) comply with applicable law, legal process or enforce our site policies. If we sell all or part of our business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, we may transfer all information mentioned herein to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of such transaction. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may change from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so you should check it frequently. 

### About Us 

This website is owned by Premiumsoft  
admin@my-tools-app.com
